首盘她拖到6比4才拿下
可最后9局
贝莱克只赢了一局
北京时间8月23日早上 快8点
WTA1000辛辛那提半决赛
贝莱克对高芙
两人生涯第一次交手
贝莱克是这一站最大的黑马
非种子的她连过普利斯科娃
萨巴伦卡
凯斯和克雷奇科娃4位名将
一路杀进半决赛 今天
她第一次撞上了高芙
首盘她不是没机会
贝莱克顶住过破发点
比分一路拉锯
Coco can celebrate the first set.
科科可以为这一盘庆祝了
One like that certainly had to work
这一盘她要费更大力气
a lot harder for it in the latter stages
才能在后半段拿下
as Bejlek brought some of her very best to bear.
贝莱克拿出了她最好的表现
The American pips her to it, 6 比 4.
这位美国人以六比四险胜
次盘 高芙的一发一分没丢
10次一发得分 全部拿下
贝莱克这边
一发再落地
也一分没能接回来
Coco Gauff is back in the final in Cincinnati.
高芙重新杀回了辛辛那提决赛
Champion 3 years ago.
三年前她在这里夺过冠
She brings to an end a brilliant week by Sara Bejlek.
她终结了贝莱克这精彩的一周
So many great names that she has taken out,
淘汰了这么多响亮的名字
but Gauff was having none of it tonight.
可高芙今晚不给她机会
Took charge early, fended off the fight back well enough,
她早早掌控局面，稳稳挡住反扑
and then stormed to the finish line
然后一路冲向终点
and is deservedly into her eighth WTA 1000 final
闯进生涯第八个1000赛决赛
in her career and her third of the year.
也是本季第三个
Will this be the one that she finally gets to win?
这一次，她能拿下吗？